Tamara Falcó could be pregnant
Tamara falcó podría estar embarazada
Kiko Hernández and her husband
Kiko Hernández junto a su marido
will present the chimes this New
presentarán las campanadas este fin de
Year's Eve Anabel Pantoja explodes and gets
año Anabel Pantoja estalla y se enfada
very angry with the party program due to a
muchísimo con el programa fiesta por un
comment by Aurelio Manzano strong
comentario de Aurelio Manzano fuertes
rumors about Jorge Javier working at
rumores de Jorge Javier trabajando en
Netflix new information about the night of
Netflix nuevos datos sobre la noche de
love that Bárbara Rey and Chelo
amor que tuvieron Bárbara rey y Chelo
García Cortés had in addition Marta Riesco
García Cortés además Marta riesco
uses this interview they have given
utiliza esta entrevista que han dado
to throw a dart at Antonio
para lanzar un dardo contra Antonio
David Flores Antonio Rossi attacks
David flores Antonio Rossi arremete
Rocío Carrasco and accuses her of being a
contra Rocío Carrasco y la señala de
complainant Isabel Pantoja Beta to her
querulante Isabel Pantoja Beta a sus
children because this This is a
hijos atentos porque esto Esto es un
bit macabre of His future funeral Falete
poco macabro de Su futuro funeral Falete
very good friend of Isabel Pantoja do not secr this
muy amigo de Isabel Pantoja no secr esta
information Ana María Ald tells How was
información Ana María ald cuenta Cómo ha
her reunion with her daughter Gem
sido su reencuentro con su hija gem
Aldón after having been separated
aldón después de haber estado separadas
and socialite disappoints her fan with her
y socialité decepciona a su fan con su
new image change all this and much
nuevo cambio de imagen todo esto y mucho
more here on your favorite heart Channel
más aquí en vuestro Canal del corazón
How are you my lords How have
favorito Qué tal mi señoreros Cómo
you spent the weekend
habéis pasado el fin de semana
excuse me that I have not been able to do
disculpadme que no he podido hacer
live but I have been very busy you
directo pero es que he estado muy liado
know that  I have three channels and I
ya sabéis que tengo tres canales y no me
can't divide myself any further I give everything I can
puedo dividir más doy todo lo que puedo
This video in particular is worth it I'm going to
vale Este vídeo en concreto os voy a
ask you a favor I'm going to ask you to
pedir un favor os voy a pedir que lo
rate it double or triple double or
valoré el doble o el triple el doble o
triple what you normally rate my
el triple de lo que valoráis mi
content is worth because it
contenido normalmente vale porque es que
turns out that I was recording it and when I
resulta que lo estaba grabando y cuando
was almost at the end I was
iba ya casi por el final lo estaba
recording it without sound dude I was
grabando sin sonido quillo lo estaba
recording it without sound so it gets really
grabando sin sonido entonces da mucha
annoying it's really lazy I'll try to
rabia da mucha pereza intentaré
comment on everything again I'll try I'm not
comentarlo todo de nuevo intentaré no lo
going to do it I have to inform So
voy a hacer tengo que informar Así que
nothing it's the second time that I'm going to record
nada es la segunda vez que voy a grabar
This video I ask you all please
Este vídeo Os pido a todos por favor que
at least give me a like share
por lo menos me deis like lo compartáis
all those things please I'm Javi
todas esas cosas por favor Soy Javi
Oliveira welcome one more day to my
oliveira bienvenidos un día más a mi
channel this is telesalseo this channel is
canal esto es telesalseo este canal se
called telesalseo but this program is
llama telesalseo pero este programa es
the lollipop in this program that I try to
la piruleta en este programa que intento
upload every half day I will inform you
subir todos los medios días te informaré
of all the news of the heart CR I
de todas las noticias del corazón CR I
social news from television that have come
social noticias de la tele que hayan
out during the day so that you are
salido en el día para que estés
fully informed in an
completamente informado de una forma
entertaining way here you will find out about everything
entretenida aquí te enterarás de todo
family if you are interested in this type of
familia si te interesa este tipo de
content and you like what  I
contenido y te gusta lo que hago
subscribe by activating the bell and you will
suscríbete activando la campanita y
automatically become part
automáticamente entrarás a formar parte
of this family that we are forming
de esta familia que estamos formando
now if I don't go on too much longer because I don't
ahora sí no me enrollo mucho más que no
want this to go on forever
quiero que esto se me haga eterno Por
Please are you very interested in the gossip that I am
favor os interesa mucho el chisme que os
going to tell you in this video Things
voy a comentar en este vídeo La cosa
are on fire This video is very
está que arde Este vídeo viene muy
loaded you know that when I
cargadito ya sabéis que cuando os lo
promise you it is like this I do not sell smoke
prometo es que es así no vendo humo
make yourselves comfortable and let's go to the
poneros cómodos y vamos al
[Music]
[Música]
mess it turns out that the papari Sergio
lío resulta ser que el papari Sergio
Garrido has returned to the program fiesta if
Garrido ha vuelto al programa fiesta si
I'm not mistaken and I'm not surprised we gave
no me equivoco y no me extraña dimos
the exclusive here two three or four
aquí la exclusiva hace dos tres o cuatro
months ago that he had had certain
meses de que había tenido ciertos
problems with the program because uh
problemas con el programa porque eh A
Well papachi is dedicated to selling
bueno papachi se dedica a vender
images and apparently they would have caught him
imágenes y al parecer le habrían pillado
selling material supposedly
vendiendo material supuestamente
selling images not to another
vendiendo imágenes no a otro programa de
competing program to son soles okay they
la competencia a son soles vale esto nos
made this reach us and we gave it
lo hicieron llegar y lo dimos nosotros
exclusively and I think it was like that because
en exclusiva y creo que fue así porque
in fact he has not appeared at
de hecho no ha vuelto a aparecer por
fiestas again since then now for whatever
fiestas desde entonces ahora por lo que
reason they have fixed things they will have
sea pues han arreglado las cosas habrán
talked and it is understood it is a papari has to
hablado y se entiende es un papari tiene
live off this  has to sell
que vivir de esto tiene que vender
images It turns out that the exclusive
imágenes Resulta ser que la exclusiva
that has brought today is a bomb, I mean if
que ha traído hoy es una bomba o sea si
this is true in the news of the month and it
se cumple esto en la noticia del mes y
is quite likely that the
es bastante probable que se cumpla los
indications that we have will be true, she had that type that
indicios que tenemos tenía la tipia esa
draws my attention that she has
me llama mucha atención que lleve los
open laces and that the belly goes
cordones abiertos y que la tripita se va
out at the front let's see also It
por encima de por delante a ver también
is true that Tamara Falcó already announced
Es verdad que Tamara falcó ya anunció
this and already warned that this was going to happen that
esto y ya avisó que esto iba a pasar que
the moment she got married she was going to look to
en el momento que se casase iba a buscar
be a mother another super important fact that
ser mamá otro dato super importante que
for me this is also the same as everything that was
para mí este también es igual que todo
agreed upon that I think is quite
lo quedado que creo que son bastante
interesting is that she has been in one
interesantes es que ella ha estado en un
of the most luxurious hotels in Ibiza which
hotel de los más lujosos de de Ibiza que
is the six senses and when she was
es el six senses y cuando ella ha estado
one of those days in the spa it was mentioned
uno de esos días en el spa se comentó
that she did not do things that everyone does
que no hizo cosas que hace todo el mundo
in the spa There are things There are things, there are
en el spa Hay cosas Hay cosas no hay
things that in the spa when you are pregnant you
cosas que en el spa al estar embarazad
do not do them, the sauna whatever it is, well, it is not we
no las haces la sauna lo que sea pues
are advancing a little that you
sea no lo estamos adelantos un poco que
cannot put one in It is that for me that
la no se puede meter una Es que para mí
super important fact, well it seems
ese dato superimportante pues parece ser
that according to Serg Garrido in the
que según cuenta serg Garrido en el
program Fiesta they would have caught  with
programa fiesta habrían pillado con un
photographs that prove it Tamara
fotografías que lo demuestran a Tamara
falcó leaving a pharmacy with an
falcó saliendo de una farmacia con una
attitude that would
actitud que
indicate quite a few signs that she
indicaría bastantes indicios de que
might have gone out to buy a
podría haber salido de comprar un
predictor we have a video where you can
predictor tenemos un vídeo donde
actually see how they enter And how I
efectivamente se ve cómo entran Y cómo
asked Airport Pharmacy I
pregunt Farmacia del aeropuerto de I
visa could have witnessed a
visa podría haber sido testigo de un
very important moment in the life of
momento muy importante en la vida de
Tamara falcó eneva Friday the 13th of account to
Tamara falcó eneva Viernes 13 de cuen
make a stop there is something that could be
que hacer una parada hay algo que podría
worrying the couple and they
estar preocupando a la pareja y
prefer to clear their doubts before
prefieren despejar sus dudas antes de
starting their getaway Tamara decides to enter
empezar su escapada Tamara decide entrar
this pharmacy she does it without even
en esta farmacia lo hace sin ni siquiera
letting go of her suitcase in addition because certain
soltar la maleta además pues ciertas
faces and certain smiles could
caras y ciertas sonrisas podrían
indicate that the result would be
indicarnos que el resultado sería
positive While she is
positivo Mientras ella está en el
inside we see Yñigo Nieva walks very still He
interior vemos a yñigo nieva muy quieto
looks at his cell phone He places his leg
camina Mira el móvil coloca la pierna
on the seats and lowers it again He
sobre los asientos la vuelve a bajar
looks from one side to the other the wait
Mira hacia un lado y a otro la espera
seems to be taking forever
parece estar haciéndose la eterna
minutes later a camera
minutos más tarde una cámara
Apparently tense leaves the pharmacy
Aparentemente tensa sale de la farmacia
together they leave the airport while they
juntos abandonan el aeropuerto mientras
seem to talk about what they have in
parecen hablar de lo que se traen entre
mind but judging by the smiles that
manos pero a juzgar por las sonrisas que
appear on their faces everything indicates that they are
se dibujan en sus caras todo apunta que
expecting good news apparently then there
esperan buenas noticias al parecer luego
was a  called the pharmacy I
hubo una llamada a la farmacia me
imagine to check and confirm
imagino que para comprobar y confirmar
the good interpretation of that test
la bueno la interpretación de ese test
but we still don't know the result
pero todavía no sabemos el resultado
we want to contrast this information and we
queremos contrastar esta información y
speak with the pharmacist Hello how are you
hablamos con la farmacéutica Hola Qué
How are you was also the F with the one who
tal Cómo estás era tamb la F con la que
just attended No yes I tell you it is
acaba de atender No sí ya os digo es
quite likely that this news will be
bastante probable que esta noticia se
confirmed if not now then it will be in
confirme si no es ahora pues será en
another attempt or so we hope No because
otro intento o eso esperamos No porque
if not it would be bad news and there is no
si no serían malas noticias y no neit
pregnancy Iñ Cona and Tamara
unun de embarazo están iñ cona y Tamara
Falcó are expecting a baby what a commitment they
falcó Esperando un bebé vaya compromiso
put the pharmacist in, I mean they
en el que ponen a la farmacéutica o sea
ask the girl if she
le preguntan a la muchacha si de acá ha
went out from here to buy a property and that can't be
salido a comprar un predito y eso no se
done that can't be said
puede hacer eso no se puede decir
Imagine that suddenly she gets her
Imagínate que de repente le coge con las
defenses down and says yes to the
defensas bajas y le dice que sí al
daddy and the daddy publishes the audio there
papari y el papari publica ahí el audio
not with the pharmacist telling it and it gets her into
no con la farmacéutica contándolo y la
trouble you all know that it's
mete en un marrón todos sabéis que no es
no secret that Kiko Hernández has a
ningún secreto que Kiko Hernández tiene
very good relationship with Melilla And well, they have
muy buena relación con melilla Y bueno
done several collaborations they have done
pues han hecho varias colaboraciones no
several little things several events
han hecho varias cosillas varios evenos
no Well, it turns out that Kiko Hernández
no Pues resulta ser que Kiko Hernández
has a new job  After what
tiene un nuevo trabajo después de lo que
they recorded on Netflix, I imagine that
han grabado en Netflix yo me imagino que
for this they will have asked permission, they will have
para esto habrán pedido permiso habrá
asked permission because with Netflix as far
pedido permiso porque con Netflix hasta
as I know they have exclusivity and
donde yo sé pues tienen exclusividad y
especially when there is so much rumor
sobre todo cuando está tanto el run run
that there may be a second
de que puede que haya una segunda
season or even a new broadcast of
temporada o incluso una nueva emisión de
salv mediario on Stream on
salv mediario en Stream en el propio
Netflix itself. But well, since it is an
Netflix pero bueno como es una cosa
important thing, it is a beautiful thing. Hey, these
importante es una cosa guapa y Oye esta
people, let's see, there are collaborators who are
gente no a ver hay colaboradores que se
going to other networks. But those who
están yendo a otras cadenas Pero los que
are so telecinero, not like Kiko
son así tan tel cineros no como Kiko
Hernández, who is not just a
Hernández que no es que sea un
journalist, he is from Big Brother, he is not a
periodista es de gran hermano no es un
collaborator, he is a very Tele5 face,
colaborador es una cara muy de tele5 no
these people are going to have a more difficult time
esta gente lo van a tener más complicado
finding another job so everything
para encontrar otro curro entonces todo
that comes up has to be taken advantage of and
lo que salga hay que aprovecharlo y
also a beautiful thing are the chimes
además una cosa guapa son las campanadas
and there is nothing wrong with any of them and
y no tiene nada de malo ninguno y
neither let's see, nothing happens. No,
tampoco a ver tampoco pasa nada no
then I understand that they will have given
entonces entiendo que le habrán dado
permission and Kiko Hernández along with her
permiso y Kiko Hernández junto a su
husband Fran Antón and a certain Alejandra
marido Fran Antón y una tal Alejandra
Acere, who I don't know if she will be a presenter or
acere que no sé si será presentadora o
someone from the city council, okay, I have
será alguien del ayuntamiento vale he
tried to find information about
intentado encontrar información sobre
her, I am very sorry I have not found
ella lo siento mucho no he encontrado
anything, are going to present the chimes this
nada van a presentar las campanadas este
year on television in Melilla Anabel
año en la televisión de melilla Anabel
Pantoja has become very angry with the
Pantoja se ha enfadado mucho con el
program Fiesta it has been a while since she
programa fiesta ya hacía tiempo que
had some tension in the relationship with
tenía cierta tirantez en la relación con
this program on Tele5 a channel in which she
este programa de tele5 cadena en la que
continues working in fact we are going to see
sigue trabajando de hecho vamos a ver
some images because they have coincided today she did
unas imágenes porque han coincidido hoy
not have to go to see makeup
no ha tenido que ir an ver a maquillaje
and they have coincided And it turns out
y han coincidido Y es que Resulta ser
that Aurelio Manzano Well he said some
que Aurelio Manzano Pues dijo unas
words that Could have been very
palabras que Podrían haber sido muy
unfortunate or a little unfortunate and
desafortunadas o un poco desafortunada y
would have made Anabel Pantoja very angry there
habrían hecho cabrearse mucho aabel
are also many colleagues on
Pantoja hay muchos compañeros además en
the set who reproach her And the thing is that
el plató que se la recriminan Y es que
Aurelio would come to say that Anabel
Aurelio vendría a decir que Anabel
Pantoja always needs someone by her side to
Pantoja necesita siempre alguien al lado
hold her purse because above all
que le sujete el bolso porque sobre todo
Aurelio's phrase that she wants a
la frase de Aurelio de ella quiere un
boyfriend to carry her purses is
novio para que le lleve los bolsos pues
not very successful and it is not very pretty
no está muy acertada y no es muy bonita
and as you can understand a woman can
y como comprenderás una mujer se puede
feel offended by that phrase let's see I do
sentir ofendida con esa frase a ver yo
n't know how you interpret these
no sé como ustedes interpreta estas
words I take them as something let's see it
palabras yo me las tomo como algo a ver
is an unfortunate comment it is an
es un comentario desafortunado es un
ugly comment but I  I don't understand
comentario feo pero yo no lo entiendo
how you're interpreting this thing about
como lo están interpretando ello de que
Anabel buying her boyfriend, I rather
Anabel compre a su novio yo más bien lo
interpret it as the typical person, don't
interpreto como la típica personaa no
you have any friends, no, any
tenéis ustedes algún amigo no alguna
friend, the typical person who always
amiga la típica persona que siempre
needs to have a partner, who always ca
necesita tener una pareja que siempre
n't be alone and that is
que no puede estar sola y eso eso hace
harmful, especially to a woman, like
daño sobre todo a una mujer como dice
she says, who has been working and
ella que lleva trabajando y y
we were fighting, tell her, tell her, Anabel already
luchábamos d dile dile Anabel que ya
has my phone number and if she wants, she can
tiene mi teléfono y que si quiere que me
call me, boo, let's leave it, Anabel
llame a mí buo vamos a dejar que Anabel
LL, we are on Direct, they are listening. I
LL estamos en Direct están escuchando me
find it so ugly what I just saw
parece tan feo lo que acabo de ver por
from people who are sitting there
parte de personas que están ahí sentadas
who have experience, a job, and
que tienen una experiencia un trabajo Y
an education that I think this
una educación que creo que la tiene esta
girl who did the report has, who
chica que ha hecho el reportaje que
has all my respect because she is a
tiene todo mi respeto porque es
journalist, I think she was wrong,
periodista creo que se ha equivocado
but completely comparing me with the fact that I
pero de lleno comparándome de que yo
buy people off just to buy a
compro a la gente por comprar una
shoe, you have never given it away,
zapatilla tú no la has regalado nunca tú
not a shoe. Well, yes, you tell me
no una zapatilla Pues sí decirme ustedes
in the comments box how you
en la caja de comentarios cómo lo
love him or Ana María, how you are
amor o Ana María al Don que están
quite angry with Aurelio. Sorry, he
bastante enfadadas con Aurelio Perdona
is very strong and what about Aurelio,
es que es muy fuerte y lo de Aurelio
Aurelio, man  say that they carry my
Aurelio tío decir que a mí me llevan los
bags sorry I have I have a heart
bolsos perdona Yo tengo yo tengo corazón
And what I say hurts me I respect you I
Y a mí me duele lo que decí yo respeto
see you every time I can I see you you have to
os veo cada vez que puedo os veo tenéis
measure your words a little I understand
que medir un poco las palabras entiendo
that there is freedom Forgive me for a
que está la libertad Perdóname un
moment okay Why do you talk about
momento vale Porque habláis todos los
me every weekend whenever you feel like it
fines de semana de mí cada vez que os da
and I'll
la gana y os
take stock of what I say because I'm
inventário la que hablo porque yo estoy
telling my truth nobody has left
contando mi verdad nadie ha dejado
any job for me I left my life in
ningún trabajo por mí yo dejé mi vida en
Seville and Madrid to go to the Canary Islands
Sevilla y en Madrid para irme a Canarias
For Love Okay and that person who
Por Amor Vale y esa persona que ahora
is now by my side is working in her
está a mi lado está trabajando en su
clinic in Córdoba and what she doesn't want is to
clínica de Córdoba y lo que no quiere es
stop working to be by my side
dejar de trabajar por estar a mi lado
because she doesn't want to be supported by
porque no quiere que esté mantenido por
anyone too You're going to criticize you're also
nadie también lo Vais a criticar también
going to say that who buys my partners that's
vais a decir eso que compra mis parejas
fine I don't mess with any of
ya está bien no me meto con ninguno de
you I don't talk about you also they
vosotros no hablo de vosotros también
had an episode in which Aurelio
han tenido un episodio en el que Aurelio
Manzano wanted to meet
Manzano se ha querido encontrar con
Anabel in the corridors of Tele5
Anabel por los pasillos de tele5
while she arrived to work
mientras que ella llegaba para trabajar
on another program and she was getting into
en otro programa y se estaba metiendo en
makeup and Anabel Well she didn't want to
maquillaje y Anabel Pues no ha querido
meet him  It has obviously been
encontrarse con él evidentemente ha sido
a tense and somewhat uncomfortable situation
una situación tensa y un poco incómoda
but Anabel says no that she does not want to
pero Anabel dice que no que no quiere
give her any type of content and
regalarle ningún tipo de contenido y de
show to the party entering Anel
espectáculo a fiesta entrando Anel
no show the truth on TV whenever you
ningún show la verdad a tele cuando
want we have the phone and we talk I'm not going
quiera tenemos el teléfono y hablamos no
to do any show nor am I going to give
voy a hacer ningún show ni voy a regalar
anything to the party come on I'm telling you no we don't
nada a fiesta vamos te lo digo no no lo
talk but I'm not going to do a show
hablamos pero no voy a hacer show Aquí
Not here here no then we'll talk no no then we'll
no aquí no luego hablamos no no luego
talk I'm sorry Excuse me
hablamos Lo siento Perdona me me dejáis
please let me have something that well the reporter
por favor algo que bueno la reportera la
has followed her to makeup but Anabel
ha seguido hasta maquillaje pero Anabel
is very very very angry with the party
está muy muy muy muy enfadada con fiesta
but she has left I run it's that she told me
pero se ha ido corro es que me ha dicho
no no run I run come in come in she
que no no corras corro entra entra se
's coming in here Okay but now she's
está entrando por aquí Bueno pero ya se
leaving the one coming in is love Hello love you've
va la que entra es amor Hola amor que
come in Anabel Anabel they're
has entrado Anabel Anabel me están
telling me not to say how you are I've
diciendo que no digas cómo estás Te he
told you to give me ahas please I asked you
dicho que me de ahas por favor te lo ped
now but Aurelio has ignored him
ya pero Aurelio lo ha ignorado por
completely to the party he doesn't want to give her anything
completo a fiesta no quiere darle nada
What do you all think of this thing now
Qué pensáis ustedes de esta movida ya
but we want you to be calmer
pero queremos que estés más tranquila
tremendous Eh This is tremendous nothing they
tremendo Eh Esto es tremendo nada que
say that I buy affection and that I buy
dicen que compro cariño y que compro a
the  guys please let me go Thank you you
los tíos me dejas por favor
know that the rumors of a
Gracias ya sabéis que los rumores de una
possible edition of sálvame diario on
posible edición de sálvame diario en
Netflix are getting louder and louder and
Netflix suenan cada vez más fuertes y
everything will depend on the audience and the
todo dependerá de la audiencia y el
performance of the premiere of
funcionamiento que tenga el estreno de
that real one that they recorded in America It
ese real que han grabado en América
depends on how it works and how well it works
Depende cómo funcione y depende la
because they will make a salvame
[__] que tenga pues harán un salvame
diario on Stream on Netflix it is very
diario en Stream en Netflix es muy
likely that what is being rumored is true
probable que sea verdad esto que se está
at the moment it is an option that is being
rumoreando de momento es una opción que
considered and sources
se está planteando y lo dicen Fuentes
close to Netflix say that Jorge Javier will be
cercanas a Netflix que Jorge Javier sea
the presenter to see This is something that
el presentador a ver Esto es algo que
was more than anything logical if the
más que nada era lógico si se adapta el
format is adapted again to a newspaper because
formato otra vez a un diario pues hay
a presenter must be found unless
que buscar un presentador a no ser que
one of the collaborators who
lo haga alguno de los colaboradores que
are already participating in the reality show does it Well, it
están participando ya en el reality Pues
will be Jorge or will they call a new one, which is
será Jorge o llamarán a uno nuevo lo
logical and ideal now that he has lost his
lógico y lo ideal ahora que se ha
job with the
quedado sin trabajo con lo de cuentos
Chinese tales thing Well, Jorge will do it
chinos Pues será que lo haga Jorge
talking about Netflix has published an
hablando de Netflix ha publicado una
interview of Chelo García Cortés with
entrevista de Chelo García Cortés con
Bárbara Rey in which they talk again
Bárbara Rey en las que vuelven a hablar
about their night of passion that night of
de su noche de pasión esa noche de
passion that has been so talked about
pasión que tanto ha dado que hablar
for so long and about which so many
durante tanto tiempo y de los que tantos
memes have come out  also a
memes han salido también una historia
romantic story a love story a
romántica una historia de amor una
story that the flag The LGBT And they also
historia que a bandera El lgtb Y además
use it a lot and
lo utilizan mucho y se recuerdan mucho
the clips are remembered a lot but today we don't find out
los clips pero que hoy no nos enteramos
about an ingredient that we didn't
de un ingrediente con el que no
count on we didn't know and it changes
contábamos no lo sabíamos y cambia
a lot of things no And it's that despite the fact that
muchas cosas no Y es que a pesar de que
these two were there a little bit further
estas dos estuvieran ahí un poquito más
apart and so on no and with genier better they
aparte y demás no y con genier mejor no
weren't alone that night of love that
estaban solas esa noche de amor que dice
Barbara says I had one well That first
Bárbara yo tuve una pues Esa primera
night of love we weren't alone we were
noche de amor no estábamos solas éramos
five people I never said two
cinco personas nunca he dicho de dos
because because the night of love I mean
porque porque la noche de amor O sea no
we didn't become independent in the group let's see
nos independizamos en el grupo a ver yo
what I understand here is an orgy I don't know
lo que entiendo aquí es una [__] no sé
how you understand it because she did
cómo lo entendéis ustedes porque es que
n't pay much attention to us either I mean neither I mean well that's it
tampoco nos prestaba mucha atención o
and
sea que tampoco O sea pues ya está y
Chelo has said that we've had more than
Chelo ha contado que hemos tenido más de
one night let's leave it at one Chelo
una noche vamos a dejarlo en una Chelo
you know it's not true we don't coincide
tú sabes que no es cierto no coincidimos
at night It's okay
en las noches No pasa nada esta charla
Marta Riesco has taken advantage of this chat who has
la ha aprovechado Marta riesco que ha
shared on her Instagram account
compartido en su cuenta de Instagram
some phrases from Barbara Rey with which we
unas frases de Bárbara Rey con las que
understand that when you are
entendemos que cuando la estás
publishing is that you feel
publicando es que te sientes
identified and empathize with Barbara
identificada y empatizas con Bárbara
because it is the first thing that I should have
porque es lo primero que yo tendría que
demanded in my life from any
haber exigido en mi vida a cualquier
person who was looked at that they not
persona que estuviera mirado que no me
hide me because I do not believe that here I have to
escondieran porque yo no creo que aquí a
hide and of that type I have
mí haya que esconderme y de ese tipo he
had many times so much need for
tenido muchas veces tanta necesidad de
affection that I have allowed not to hide Noa
cariño que he permitido no esconde Noa
de nocho there are many people who are
de nocho hay mucha gente que está
criticizing Marta Lance this dart to
criticando que Marta Lance este dardo a
Antonio David because this is a dart
Antonio David porque esto es un dardo
for Antonio David Flores and Well there are
para Antonio David flores y Bueno hay
many other people who are saying that
otra mucha gente que está diciendo que
this is a reality that we have
esto es una realidad que hemos visto
all seen in public no what is
todos en público no lo que sí que es
true and I think that in all of this we will
verdad y creo que en todo esto estaremos
agree is that yes you can feel
de acuerdo es que sí te puedes sentir
identified it may be a die it
identificada puede ser un dado incluso
may even be a reality but in the end you
puede ser una realidad pero que al final
have to turn the page at some point
hay que pasar página en algún momento
that several months have passed and I say this
que han pasado Ya varios meses y lo digo
as advice to women any
como un consejo a las mujeres cualquier
man who wants to hide you bad the
hombre que quiera esconderte malo el
man or the woman who is whatever it is
hombre que o la mujer sean lo que sea
with a person has to be
esté con una persona tiene que estar
happy and proud of that person and and
feliz y orgullosa de de esa persona y y
of showing off that person and taking them
de presumir de esa persona y de llevarla
everywhere you know that this week there
a todas partes ya sabéis que esta semana
was a very  sounded on the
ha habido una sentencia muy sonada en
networks and it is the sentence that
redes y es la sentencia que ha perdido
Rocío Carrasco has lost in the Supreme Court
en el tribunal supremo Rocío Carrasco
against Kiko Matamoros It turns out that
contra Kiko Matamoros Resulta ser que
everyone is talking about this and
todo el mundo está hablando de esto y
there are some media that have made a
hay algunos medios que han hecho una
compilation of all the lawsuits that
recopilación de todas las demandas que
Rocio Carrasco loses Antonio Rossi has not
pierde roso Carrasco Antonio Rossi no se
held back and despite the fact that he
ha cortado un pelo y a pesar de que
has a good relationship with them and there are
tiene buena relación con ellos y hay
times when we have heard how he
veces que hemos escuchado cóm se
met and they have been chatting at
encontrado y han estado Charlando en
parties and things like that, he has not
fiestas y cosas por el estilo no se ha
held back in pointing at Rocío
cortado un pelo en señalar a Rocío
Carrasco and saying that she is a complainant
Carrasco y decir que es una querulante
Rocío Carrasco is a complainant a brief message
Rocío Carrasco es una querulante mensaje
to the forceful park that
escueto a la parque contundente el que
Antonio
ha publicado hace unos minutos Antonio
Rossi, the Tele5 collaborator, published a few minutes ago on
Rossi el colaborador de tele5 en redes
social networks it has been a while since we saw
sociales hacía tiempo que no veíamos a
a collaborator of the Mediaset chain
un colaborador de la cadena de mediaset
speak out about the daughter of Rocío
pronunciarse acerca de la hija de Rocío
Jurado who we already know that for
Jurado quien ya sabemos que desde hace
months has been on that list of
meses se encuentra en esa lista de
vetoed characters no one wants to
personajes her vetados nadie quiere
even pronounce her name after her
siquiera pronunciar su nombre después de
time on that Chain in which
que pasase por esa Cadena en la que no
the grass has not grown again and which has been
ha vuelto a crecer la hierba y que se ha
assumed to be in the greatest of ruins  since
asumido en la mayor de las ruinas desde
her docuseries things are once again a
su docuserie vuelve a estar la cosa un
bit tense between
poco tensa por cierto entre la
Ana Rosa Quintana's production company and the
productora de Ana Rosa Quintana y la
TV factory we already know that this
fábrica de la tele ya sabemos que esta
war goes back a long way But now later
guerra viene de lejos Pero ahora después
we are going to comment on some news that would be
vamos a comentar una noticia que sería
the last of all But first of all
la última de todas Pero antes de nada
let's see that news that
vamos a ver esa noticia a la que hace
Antonio Rossi alludes to when referring to
alusión Antonio Rossi para referirse a
Roito as the plaintiff here we have it
roito como la querulante aquí la tenemos
news from the look portal all the
noticia del portal look todos los
celebrities who have been denounced by
famosos que han sido denunciados por
Rocío Carrasco and who have won you already
Rocío Carrasco y que la han ganado ya
know that fider al bak's wife
sabéis que la mujer de fider al bak
continues to add defeats in court
sigue sumando derrotas en los tribunales
the last of all very famous also
la última de todas muy sonada también
against Kiko Matamoros in the supreme court and the
contra Kiko Matamoros en el supremo y lo
truth is it is a reality of course that
cierto Es una realidad desde luego que
this woman demands a lot but what is to
esta mujer demanda mucho pero lo que es
win wins little to say nothing
ganar gana poco por no decir nada ha
something has happened they gave some news today
pasado una cosa han dado una noticia hoy
on socialite that has left me a little
en socialite que me ha dejado un poco
crazy and that is that Isabel Pantoja would be
loco y es que Isabel Pantoja estaría
planning in some way that her children
planeando de alguna manera que sus hijos
could not attend
no pudieran asistir el día de mañana a
her funeral tomorrow I understand that it will be
su funeral entiendo que estará siendo
like some kind of document leaving it
como una especie de documento dejándolo
signed before a notary but it already
firmado ante notario pero es que ya me
seems macabre to me to do something like that eh  to
parece macabro hacer algo así eh para
plan something while you're dead, I
planear algo mientras que estés muerta o
mean, I understand that in the end there are things that have to be
sea entiendo que al final hay cosas que
done I don't understand that you have to
hay que hacer No entiendo que tienes que
leave it in writing The inheritances and those
dejar por escrito Las herencias y esas
things no but getting into it To prepare what
cosas no pero ya liarte a A preparar lo
the funeral is and the characters or the
que es el funeral y los personajes o las
people who are going to be banned from
personas que van a estar vetados a
entering anyway it seems very very macabre to me
entrar en fin me parece muy muy macabro
no especially macabre with everything
no sobre todo eso macabro con todo lo
Knowing that Pantoja doesn't want the
Sabiendo sabel Pantoja no quiere que el
day that her children are not there nor the people
día que no esté ni sus hijos ni la gente
from television nor absolutely anyone that
de la televisión ni absolutamente nadie
it becomes a parade of
aquello se convierta en un desfile de de
people crying Beatriz Cortaz has given the
gente llorando Beatriz cortaz ha dado la
news on Federico's program and
noticia en el programa de Federico y
affirms Well that it is because Isabel
Afirma Pues que se debe a que Isabel
Pantoja does not want a spectacle she does not
Pantoja no quiere un espectáculo no
want a media show she does not want a
quiere un show mediático no quiere un
gossip show there she does not want a
programón del corazón allí no quiere un
parade of people crying the day she
desfile de gente llorando el día que
dies she wants her children far away from
muera quiere a sus hijos muy lejos de
her her daughter responds bluntly now how
ella su hija responde tajante ahora cómo
things are so much war and so much
están las cosas tanta Guerra y tanta
death not talking about these things of a
muerte no hablar de estas cosas de un
supposition seems a little A little ugly to me
supuesto me parece un poco Un poco feo
there are things that come out in life and not in
hay que me sale en la vida y no en cosas
negative things and she only wants her
negativ y solo quiere que esté allí su
closest and most  Loyal I
núcleo eh más cercano y más Leal
understand that a very very small nucleus
entiendo que un núcleo muy muy pequeño
wants to leave absolutely silently
quiere irse absolutamente en silencio
with its hard core that are few loyal
con su núcleo duro que son pocos ileales
also they would also be affirming that
además también estarían afirmando que
the intention behind this is
esto la intención que tiene detrás es
that the children well This counting on
que los hijos bueno Esto contando con
that this This story not in this
que esto Esta historia no en esta
story the children do not enter at the moment
historia no entran los hijos de momento
no I mean if everything remains the same from here to I
no O sea si todo sigue igual de aquí a
hope that in many years I
Ojalá que dentro de muchos años me
refer to the death of Isabel Pantoja no
refiero a la muerte de Isabel Pantoja no
if everything remains the same I understand that
si todo sigue igual entiendo que que
Isabel does not want the children to
Isabel pues no quiere que los hijos
do business with this that they do not sell
hagan negocio con esto que no vendan
but intends to prevent her children from
pero pretende impedir que sus hijos
being able to profit from the media with her
puedan sacar rédito mediático con su
death if the situation she has with her
muerte si la situación que tiene con sus
children is what it has which is null then there will be
hijos es la que tiene que es nula pues
no changes give condolences to the
no habrá cambios darle el pésame a los
children they are going to go and tell it and they are going to earn
hijos lo van a ir a contar y van a ganar
money for it in an exclusive sure
dinero por ello en una exclusiva segur
clear as that they do not sell what I mean in the
claro como que no vendan queé O sea al
end if they want to give an
final si ellos quieren dar una
interview or whatever even if they do not go
entrevista o lo que sea aunque no vayan
to the funeral they are going to give it despite the fact that
al funeral la van a dar a pesar de que
in her return to the stage we have
en su vuelta a los escenarios hemos
seen a rolling Isabel Pantoja
visto una Isabel Pantoja rolladora
even throwing pullits to her children
incluso lanzando pullit a sus hijos a
through her songs they assure that the
través de sus canciones aseguran que la
widow of  paky r is going through the worst moment
viuda de paky r pasa por el peor momento
of her life, she is already devastated, she is
de su está ya destrozada que está
depressed because emotionally she then
hundida porque anímicamente ella luego
goes on stage and has not recovered
sale al escenario y no se ha recuperado
from the mother, she has not recovered from the
de la madre no se ha recuperado de los
children, she has not recovered from and they say
hijos no se ha recuperado de y cuentan
that the last blow the
que el último golpe que recibe la
singer receives is this week, let's not
cantante es esta misma semana no
forget that her daughter got married on
olvidemos que su hija se ha casado el
Saturday. Indeed, the damage
sábado Efectivamente es que el el daño
is a damage that according to her daughter is by her
es un daño que según su hija es por
own decision, Isabel could have
decisión propia Isabel podría haberla
accompanied her on one of the most
acompañado en uno de los días más
important days of her life, there is room for
importantes de su vida hay sitio para
everyone and whoever wanted to be has
todo el mundo y Quién ha querido estar
been. By the way, many followers
ha estado Por cierto muchos seguidores
of the social program it would be very
del programa social it estarían muy
disappointed with this program. We
decepcionados con este programa Ya
were already talking on a
estuvimos hablando en un noticiero
previous newscast that promised a change of look,
anterior que prometían un cambio de look
a change of image and in the end, well,
un cambio de imagen y al final pues
the change of image has simply been
simplemente el cambio de imagen ha sido
changing some colors, making everything
cambiar algunos colores ponerlo todo
more pink. The only thing missing is for
como más Rosa Solamente le ha faltado
Carlota corredera to come by and
por allí que se pase Carlota corredera y
the change has been for nothing. Here I
el cambio ha sido para nada por aquí os
will be putting on screen some of
estaré poniendo en pantalla algunas de
the criticisms that her
las críticas que han hecho sus
followers have made on social networks. But in the end,
seguidores en redes Pero al final pues
what is seen in a general way is not that
lo que se ve a modo así general no es
nobody liked it And that  have
que a nadie le ha gustado Y que han
been very dissatisfied regarding the
quedado muy insatisfechos respecto al
issue of Isabel Pantoja Falete has
tema de Isabel Pantoja Falete se ha
spoken out, you know that Falete is a very good
pronunciado ya sabéis que Falete es muy
friend of Isabel and well if this is
amigo de Isabel y que bueno de ser esto
true then he would have some idea or at
cierto pues tendría alguna idea o por lo
least let's see, maybe he doesn't know the
menos a ver a lo mejor no conoce las
most intimate things, not like what
cosas más íntimas no como lo que puede
Isabel could sign before the notary, what she
firmar Isabel ant el notario lo que
could prepare and above all something so
puede preparar y sobre todo algo tan
macabre, no and maybe so recent that she has
macabro no y a lo mejor tan reciente que
n't had time to discuss it with her
no le ha dado tiempo a comentar con sus
friends but according to Falete, since he knows
amigos pero según Falete como conoce a
Isabel, what they are saying doesn't add up
Isabel no le cuadra lo que están
and she is completely sure that
diciendo y está completamente segura de
this is not the case, you haven't said any
que esto no es así no has dicho n de
conflict, you know we're going to
conflicto ya sabes que te vamos a
ask you and why. Come on, no, I don't
preguntar y por qué Por venga no no lo
know, about Isabel, about your friend Isabel, she did
sé por Isabel por tu amiga Isabel hace
nothing. A day or two ago you made information
nada Hace un día o dos hac información
that she has decided to break all
de que ha decidido romper todos los
family ties, with her children, with the rest
lazos familiares con hijos con el resto
of the family, she says that when she dies she wants to
de familia dice que cuando muera quiere
die alone, that she doesn't want a funeral home, I don't
morir sola que no quiere tanatorio yo no
think that's the case eh, I don't think that's the case, no, you
creo que eso sea así eh No creo que eso
're not one of those friends who would
sea así no no eres de las amistades que
go see her, right, accompany her, if you're one
s ir a verla verdad acompañarla si eres
of those friends who loves her a lot, a
de las amistades que s que la aca mucho
lot, a lot, a lot  I don't see her but if we
mucho mucho mucho que no la veo pero si
talk from time to time how is she
hablamos de vez en cuando cómo está ella
Falete what can she tell us we don't
Falete que nos puede decir que no
know anything as far as I know well cover
sabemos nada hasta donde yo sé bien tapa
Chucha health cover Chucha health I don't
Chucha de salud tapa Chucha de salud No
know if what else the wedding Ana María
sé si de eso qué más la boda Ana María
Aldón met up with her daughter it
aldón se reencontrado con su hija ha
was Ana María's mother's birthday these last few days
sido el cumpleaños en estos últimos días
and Gema
de la madre de Ana María y Gema ha
came to this birthday party also with her
acudido a este cumpleaños además con su
daughter I mean the whole
hija O sea se han reunido toda la
family got together Ana María met with
familia se ha reunido Ana María con
Eladio together with Gema with her little one
Eladio junto a Gema con su pequeñita
So apparently they've had a
Entonces por lo visto pues han tenido un
good rapprochement things have been
acercamiento bueno la cosa se ha
resolved they're fine Ana María made
solucionado están bien Ana María Hizo
some comments that Gema Well it didn't
unos comentarios que a Gema Pues no le
sit well with on the subject of Lonely
sentó muy bien sobre el tema de Lonely
fan let's see I'm not mad at my daughter
fan a ver yo no me enfado con mi hija
because she opened a profile on an
porque ella se abra un perfil en una red
adult social network I'm not sorry but no it's not like
social para adultos no lo siento pero no
that she's mad at your
no es así se enfada ella por tu
comment that she interprets it in
comentario que ella lo interpreta a su
her own way Of course She got mad because I said that I would respect my daughter's decisions as if she wanted to be a porn actress for those who don't know and who are not familiar with the term only fan  the kids do
término only fan en la chavalería sí que
know more about this topic no only fan is a
conocen más este tema no only fan es una
social network eh that I can make a
red social eh que yo me puedo hacer una
paid account so people have to
cuenta de pago o sea la gente tiene que
pay to follow me maybe it's 5 15
pagar para seguirme A lo mejor Son 5 15
20 a month and on that social network I publish
20 al mes y yo en esa red social publico
content exclusively for these
contenido únicamente exclusivo para esta
people who pay plus you can also
gente que pagan además también puedes
pay for another service you can't pay
pagar por otro servicio no puedes pagar
for an exclusive audio you can pay
por un audio en exclusiva puedes pagar
for an exclusive video but eh There is a
por un vídeo en exclusiva pero eh Hay un
detail that must be added that is very
detalle que hay que Añadir que es muy
important no and that is that well only
importante no y es que bueno pues only
fan is for this type of things with your
fan es para este tipo de cosas con tu
fan with erotic content even
fan con contenido erótico incluso
pornographic okay it can be erotic
pornográfico vale puede ser erótico
it can be very very very risqué there are
puede ser muy muy muy subido de tono hay
times when they leave more to the
ocasiones en las que dejan más a la
imagination there are other times when they
imaginación hay otras ocasiones en las
leave less to the imagination but
que dejan menos a la imaginación pero
generally it is usually very
por lo general pues suele ser muy
erotic even pornographic I don't know what
erótico incluso pornográfico no sé cómo
gema's content will be like because I haven't
será el contenido de gema porque no lo
seen it nothing has been leaked this the
he visto no se ha filtrado nada esto el
problem that it has eh that everyone can
problema que tiene eh que cada uno puede
do with their body obviously what they
hacer con su su cuerpo evidentemente lo
want no and if you want to sell
que quiera no y y si quieres vender
photos because you like to sell photos and you don't
fotos porque te gusta vender fotos y te
care and you feel like it then perfect
da igual y te da la gana pues perfecto
no this  The problem is that it's
no esto el problema que tiene es que es
very normal, very logical, and very common for it to
muy normal y muy lógico y muy habitual
leak. I mean, imagine anyone
que se filtre O sea imagínate cualquiera
pays 20 and they start leaking it,
paga 20 y empiezan a filtrarlo que
obviously that's illegal, right? But
evidentemente eso es ilegal no pero
well, they start leaking it, they start spreading it,
bueno empiezan a filtrarlo empiezan a
right? And in the end,
difundirlo no y al final pues se queda
your intimate photos stay all over the internet, not
por todo internet tus fotos íntimas no
your erotic or pornographic photos, and
tus fotos eróticas o pornográficas y la
most people are going to see them for free, that's what
mayoría de gente las va a ver gratis eso
happens, no, she's prostituting herself,
es lo que pasa no que se prostituye por
please, it has nothing to do with it. Then
favor que no tiene nada que ver entonces
I heard the bell, but I didn't know where it
escuchó campana pero no sabía de dónde
came from, and in the end, they're bad. I understood
venía y al final son malos he entendido
that they have led us to be
que sí nos han llevado a estar un tiempo
away from the phone and everything for a while,
distanciada de teléfono y de todo
fortunately, it was resolved as
afortunadamente se ha solucionado como
expected because the first time it
era de esperar porque la primera vez que
happened to me, Ana María describes the encounter
me pasa Ana María describe el encuentro
as, well, the most normal thing in the world,
como bueno de lo más normal del mundo
everything went very well. Well, at first, I was
todo muy bien Pues bueno al principio yo
going very carefully. I mean, the
iba pues con pies de plomo digo lo
important thing was that it was
importante era que era el cumpleaños de
my mother's birthday, for me, it was the most important thing
mi madre para mí Era lo más importante
because if it hadn't been her birthday,
porque si no hubiese sido el cumpleaños
I wouldn't have gone, so starting from
yo no hubiese ido entonces partiendo de
there, well, I knew that my daughter was going to be there.
ahí pues yo sabía que iba a estar mi
I was nervous, yes, I was a
hija yo estaba nerviosa sí estaba un
little nervous, yes, there was a spark and no  that
poco nerviosa sí la una chispa y no que
Gemma has a lot of character and we
Gemma tiene mucho carácter claro y
were there eh Very well we
estuvimos ahí eh Muy bien nosotros
entered we greeted each other we gave each other two
entramos nos saludamos nos dimos dos
kisses I saw my granddaughter I ate her kiss
besos yo vi a mi nieta Me la comía beso
with the perfect goodbye So nothing the
con el adio perfecto Así que nada la
family united again I went to your partner
familia unida de nuevo iba a tu pareja
Yes also with her very well Nothing more
Sí también con ella muy bien Nada más lo
for what is normality not e
por lo que es la normalidad no e
education can not be lost I can
educación no se puede perder yo puedo
have a distance she may be a
tener un distanciamiento puede estar un
little upset with you but it does not mean that
poquito molesta contigo pero es no quita
I come in to greet you good afternoon and
de que yo entre salude buenas tardes y
give you a kiss and the truth is that we are
te de un beso y la verdad que estamos
talking every day and she has already
hablando todos los días y ya ella lo ha
said it has been spoken the conversation was
dicho se ha hablado la conversación fue
fruitful I adore my daughter I love my
fructífera yo adoro a mi hija yo quiero
daughter she is my daughter is above
a mi hija es mi hija está por encima de
all she made me a mother at 17 years old I have
todo me hizo madre con 17 años he
suffered a lot with her and she well she must have had a
sufrido mucho con ella y ella pues lo
bad time at certain times I
habrá pasado mal en ciertos momento yo
also had a
también lo pas
bad time but then there is Reconciliation there
mal pero entonces ya hay Reconciliación
is and well family here we are going to
ya hay y bueno familia por aquí vamos a
leave the video for today I hope it has been
ir dejando el vío por hoy Espero que
to your liking If you have
haya sido de vuestro agrado Si habéis
reached this part of the video I understand
llegado a esta parte del vídeo entiendo
that you like this content and if you
que os gusta este contenido y si os
like this type of content the only thing
gusta este tipo de contenido lo único
that Os  I always ask that you share when I hit the
que Os pido siempre que reventé el botón
like button. It's great that you
de like que compartáis Que bueno que os
subscribe to all those things, okay, there's no
suscribáis todas esas cosas vale no hace
need to repeat it, but it's repeated because
falta repetirlo pero se repite porque se
you forget. I send you a huge kiss. We'll
os olvida os mando un beso enorme nos
see each other later during the day with more
vemos luego durante el día con más
videos and I hope that in case we don't do a
vídeos y espero que por no hagamos un
live stream or something, I love you very much, your
directito o algo os quiero muchísimo
honor. Bye bye.
señoría chao chao un
[Music]
[Música]
kiss.
beso